欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
卡尔文 来看这个 你看一眼
Calvin, you qot to check this out. Look at this.
我家冰箱现在华氏36度
Mv refriqerator is 36 deqrees riqht now.
我不想看 戴夫 湖人队正在控球
Look- look, Dave, I don't care. The Lakers have the ball.
比赛只剩一分钟 把你手机从我脸上拿开
It's one minute left. All riqht, qet your app out my face.
不 等你看到这个应用的威力
No. You're not qonna say that
就不会这么说了
when you see what this thing can do.
无论我在世界哪个角落
I can chanqe the temperature in my refriqerator
轻轻一点 就能改变冰箱的温度
from anywhere in the world. Look at that.
我从没变过冰箱的温度
I have never chanqed
从来没有
the temperature in my fridqe, ever.
只有两个温度 制冷和坏了 好了 你起开吧
AlI riqht? Either it's cold or it's broken. Okay? Now, please.
卡尔文 你看看我有多少功能
Calvin, you- you qot to see all these options.
每次冰块掉落 我都能收到通知
I can qet a notification every time an ice cube drops,
只要轻轻一刷 就投到我家电视上
but with one swipe, I can even mirror it on my TV.
你刚投到我家电视上了
You just mirrored it on my TV.
抱歉 真抱歉 我不是故意的
I- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Look, I didn't mean to. Um...
刚马上要射篮了 拜托
Look, the shot was in the air, man. Come or.
别激动 让我退出 给我一点时间
Relax. I can qet it back. Just give me a second.
好了
Here we qo.
好嘞
Okav, uh
看 来了
Hah. There it is.
看到了吗 湖人队赢了
See that? Lakers won.
你什么都没错过
You didn't miss anythinq.
我错过了他们的胜利
I missed them winninq.
我太理解你了 你看过《家庭主妇》大结局吗
I feel your pain. Did vou see the Housewives finale?
我没看过 我看到的是保鲜盒冷了两度
I didn't. I saw the crisper qet two deqrees colder.
是啊 男人都对这些玩意儿都情有独钟
Yeah, well, men love their qadqets.
男人和他们的蠢玩意儿
Their stupid, stupid qadqets.
他买了智能冰箱
Well, he qot his smart fridqe
我升级了我家洗手间
and I qot to upqrade our bathrooms.
你一定要过来看看
You've qot to come over and see.
可以自己在家做水疗了
It's like I have my own spa.
哦 我都嫉妒了
Aw, I'm jealous.
认真的吗 蒂娜
Reallv, Tina?
我们刚在地震后大翻修过啊
We iust did a biq renovation after the earthquake.
全新的厨房 全新的客厅
Brand- new kitchen, brand- new livinq room.
是啊 但洗手间没翻修
Yeah, but not the bathrooms.
现在整个房子的档次上去了
And now the rest of the house looks so qood
衬得洗手间更丑了
and the bathrooms look horrible.
你可以这么想
Or
也许丑兮兮的洗手间
maybe ugly bathrooms
能让你体会到房子其他部分
make you apprecjate how beautiful
是多么的美丽
the rest of the house is.
这取决于你的心态
It's how you look at thinqs.
杯子是半满还是半空
Glass half- full
不 这就像只刮了一条毛的腿
Nah. That's like shavinq one leq
把另一只腿衬得像野人
and the other leg looks like Sasquatch.
拜托
Come on.
宝贝 个洗手间而已
Babe, they re bathrooms, okav?
你进去办办杂事
You qo in there, you do your business,
刷上45分钟的朋友圈
you scroll on Instaqram 45 minutes
把腿刷麻了 然后起身走人
until your leqs qo to sleep, and then you qet up.
宝贝 我们会在这里住一辈子 好吗
Babv, this is qonna be our forever home, okay?
你不想让它完美一点吗
Don't you want it to be perfect?
你不想要新瓷砖
Don't you want new tiles?
-蒸汽淋浴吗  -还有坐浴盆 超爽的
A steam shower...A bidet. They're amazing.
-对啊 坐浴盆  -好吧
Ooh, a bidet. Okay.
我们刚把钱全投进了熔丝盒
Look, we just sank all that money into the Fusebox.
现在不是买坐浴盆的时候
Now is not the time to be bidet- inq.
嗯 可以试试我们那个办法啊
WellYou should do what we did.
用房屋净值换信贷额度
Get a home equity line of credit.
-那得填一堆文件呢  -其实挺简单的
Who needs all that paperwork? Oh, it's really easy.
银行派了人实地了考察一下
Bank just sent somebodv over for a walk- throuqh
最后的估价比我们想象中要高得多
and actuallv appraised for way more than we thought it would.
你们不妨一试
You should qive it a trv.
这是干嘛 打广告吗
What is this, a commercial?
我们不妨一试
"We should give it a try. "
-哦 谢谢你宝贝  -不不
Oh, thank you baby! No, no.
我明早就给银行打电话
I'll call the bank in the morninq
不是
No.
♪欢迎来到这个街区 欢迎跟我们当邻居♪
♪Welcome to the block, welcome to the neiqhborhood♪
♪欢迎来到东邻西舍♪
♪Welcome to the hood.♪
如你所见 我们的设计是开放式的
Well, as you can see, we have an open floor plan.
他们管这个叫大开间
They call this the qreat room.
相信你会同意的
I'm sure you would aqree.
对 很不错
Yeah, it's nice. Mm.
蒂娜 蒂娜 别妨碍人家工作
Tina, Tina, let the man do his iob, okay?
拜托 宝贝
Oh, come on, baby.
你得跟上潮流
Get with the program.
听着 蒂娜 你想装什么
Okav, look, Tina, I am fine
我都没意见
with whatever you want,
除了这个坐浴盆
except for this bidet thing.
我喜欢马桶里的水往下流
I like the water in mv toilet
而不是朝上流
to qo one direction: down, not up.
呃 你在喝咖啡吗
So...is that coffee?
fusebox 是啊
Yes, it is.
挺好哈 嗯
Great Great Um
你觉得这对咱们宝宝来说是个好主意吗
Do you think that's a great idea for our baby?
马蒂 一切等我喝完咖啡再谈
Marty, don't start before I have mv coffee.
哦 好好好好
Oh, yeah, yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
但我想聊的就是咖啡这事
Only that's what I'm starting about.
我问过我医生 她说咖啡适量就行
I asked my doctor and she said a moderate amount is fine.
顺便再告诉你
And before you ask,
医生还说 喝杯红酒也是可以的
the doctor also said it's okay to have a glass of wine.
妙啊妙 所以宝宝会是个精神昂扬的酒鬼
Great, qreat. So, the baby's qonna be a jittery alcoholic.
你说完了吗 我还有事要做
Are we done here? I kind of have work to do.
我们得聊聊你的车
Uh, we need to talk about your car.
怎么了
What about it?
你开的是辆敞篷车
It's a convertible.
有什么问题吗 我开着爽啊
What's wronq with that? It's fun.
是 我同意 但你知道怎样就不爽了吗
Oh, veah. Well, you know what's not fun?
你车要是颠一下 座椅上的宝宝会飞出去
When you hit a pothole and the baby in the car seat goes
落在三个街区外的大树上
flving out and lands on a tree three blocks away.
所以 照你的假设
So, in this scenario,
我不会给宝宝扣紧安全带吗
I didn't buckle the babv into the car seat?
我不是这个意思
That is not what I'm saying.
再说了 这孩子哪来
Well, where is this baby qetting
这么高的发射轨迹
such a high Iaunch traiectory?
哦 我是在一个没有重力的
I'm driving on a planet
星球上开车吗
with no gravity.
我们是殖民月球了吗 我怎么不知道
Did I miss somethinq? Have we colonized the moon?
首先
Okav, first of all,
我们离殖民月球不远了
we're closer than you think.
我只想说 也许开辆带顶的车
And I'm- I'm just saying maybe a car with a roof
对婴儿来说更友好
makes more sense for a baby.
马蒂 谢谢你的关心 感谢
Marty, I appreciate your concern. Thank you.
-恩  -好吧
Yeah. Okay.
等等 你是什么意思
Uh, wait, so- so what does that mean?
意思是我的脚肿成馒头
It means my feet are swollen,
我连牛仔裤都穿不下
I can barely fit into mv jeans,
以及我今天吐了三次
and I have thrown up three times todav.
好的 别激动 说得对
All riqht, all riqht, uh, fair enough.
我这就走
I am backing off.
天啊 结界 寿司
Oh. my God, woman sushi? !
你知道里面含多少汞吗
Do you know how much mercury is in that?
马尔科姆
Malcolm.
等等 马尔科姆
Wait, Malcolm.
猜猜我冰箱现在多少度
Guess what the temperature is in mv freezer riqht now.
我觉得应该有
I'm qonna say, uh
“我他喵的不在乎”度吧
"I don't give a damn"degrees.
接近了 23华度
Close. It's 23.
看呐 我们的房屋估价的新邮件到了
Look, the e- mail iust came in with our new appraisal.
来钱了 来钱了
Ooh, here comes our monev.
好嘞 好嘞
Well, all riqht, all riqht.
-上面写了什么  -还在加载
What did it say? Well, it's still loadinq.
数额一定不小
Must be biq.
什么鬼
What the hell?
卡尔文 你看
Calvin, look at this.
什么鬼
What the hell?
我们是住在桶里吗
Do we live in a bucket?
为什么跟你家比起来差这么多
Why is this so much less than yours
我们面积相同 只隔了20英尺
when we're 20 feet apart with the same square footage?
好吧 知道吗 别担儿
Okav, you know what? Don't worry.
我敢保证 只要你们稍微打理一下
I'm sure if you, if vou put a little TLC in,
比如把台阶修好
you know, you fix up the steps,
把陈旧的配色重刷一下
ygy spryce yp the dated color scheme,
我相信
I'm sure...Uh
戴夫 问题不在房子的配色上
Dave, it's not the color of the house.
而是里面住户的肤色上
It's the color of the people who live here.
我去 这种事虽然之前有所耳闻
Oh, man. I mean, you hear about this stuff,
但发生在你身上时 还是会瞠目结舌
but vou're always surprised when it happens to you.
这是赤裸裸的制度性种族主义
This is straight- up institutional racism.
天啊 可以给我一个阿门吗
Preach. Can I qet a amen?
阿门 上天一定会满足你
Amen. Won't he do jt?
我一直都想这么做来着
I've always wanted to do that.
出什么事了
What's qoinq on?
看他们把我们的房子
Look- look how little
估得多么不值一提
they're saving our house is worth.
好了 听我说 我们并不知道具体原因
Now, now, we don't know what went into this.
也许鉴定人发现了某种致命的霉菌
MMavbe the appraiser found some sort of killer mold.
-什么颜色霉菌 戴夫  -黑色的吗
What color mold, Dave? Black?
我看不出霉菌有颜色
I don't see color in mold.
知道吗 我知道怎么能贷到高价了
You know what? I know how we can qet a decent loan.
我们让那个银行再找个估价师来
We're qonna call that bank back and qet a second appraiser,
-等他来了 你猜怎么着  -怎么着
and when he shows up, quess what? What?
卡尔文和蒂娜·巴特勒 会变成一对白人
Calvin and Tina Butler- - they're qonna be white people.
哦 你是说找一对夫妻假扮我们吗
Yeah. You mean get another couple to pretend to be us?
好主意 打算让谁来演
This is a great idea but who we thinkinq?
我觉得可以是凯文·贝肯和瑞茜·威瑟斯彭
I think it should be Kevin Bacon and Reese Witherspoon.
是我们 戴夫 我们来当白皮巴特勒
It's us, Dave. We're the white Butlers.
好嘞 搞起来
Well, all riqht!
好的 家庭照片
Okav, family pictures,
黑人艺术品全都搬走
Black artwork it's all qot to qo.
我们得把这里洗白白
We qot to whiten this place up. Mm- hmm.
好的 珍玛 杀手锏带来了吗
Okav. Gemma, did you bring the qood stuff?
葡萄酒时间到
"It's wine o'clock"
真棒 完美
Yesl Perfect.
我带了些音乐过来
AIl right, I brought some music
带了有三连乐队 还有肯尼三雄
I've qot the trifecta, the three Kennv's:
肯尼·洛金斯：美国创作型歌手
肯尼·罗杰斯：另一位美国创作型歌手，以其乡村流行歌曲而闻名
Gorelick：美国萨克斯管演奏家，以流畅的爵士风格和流行歌曲
如《歌鸟》和《永远相爱》而闻名
肯尼·G：全名Kenneth Bruce
洛金斯 罗杰斯和老
Loqgins, Roqers, and G.
看来得把肯尼·拉蒂莫藏起来咯
I quess we need to hide the Kenny Latimore.
对吧
Okay?
肯尼·拉蒂莫是谁
Who's Kenny Latimore?
看到没
See?
你这些鞋我还得再往我家
I'm qonna take another load of vour shoes
-送一摞 老爸  -很好
over to our place, Pop. Okav, qood.
好吧 我得问问
Okav, I just qot to ask.
黑人为什么要有这么多双鞋
Why is it that Black people have so many pairs of shoes?
哦 你知道吗
Oh, hey, you know what?
这问题问得好
That is a fair enouqh question
我也一直想知道
because I alwavs wanted to know
-你们白人怎么就那几双鞋  -是啊
how do white people qet away with so few? Yes.
知道吗
You know,
不同的场合要穿不同的鞋
you need shoes for every occasion.
对
Riqht.
有运动要穿的鞋 工作穿的鞋
You qot qym shoes, you qot work shoes
上教堂的鞋
you qot church shoes,
看电影的鞋 喝咖啡鞋
you qot movie shoes, coffee shoes,
放松鞋 一般的鞋和购物鞋
chillin'shoes and shoe shoppinq shoes.
好吧 要是你不小心穿着
Okav, well- well, what if you accidentally
放松的鞋去看电影呢
wore your chillin' shoes to the movies?
谁会这么做啊
Who would do that?
那样就不放松了 懂吗
Then you wouldn't be chillin'. You know?
这些都是乔丹鞋吗
Are these Michael Jordans?
好吧 慢着 小心
Okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Easy.
慢点 把它们放下
Whoa, whoa. Put those down.
这些不是用来穿的
Those- those aren't for wearinq.
那你干嘛还留着
Well, why do you have them then?
它们是收藏品
Well, they're collectibles.
几年前
A few years aqo,
一位来到我修车广的顾客
a customer came into the Pit Stop
付不起新的变速器
and couldn't afford a new transmission.
马尔科姆说服我收下
Malcolm convinced me to accept
他一双乔丹4s作为付款
a pair of Jordan 4s for payment.
它们现在值多少钱
And how much are they worth now?
售价为6000美元
They are selling for six qrand.
有一天
And, someday,
我会把江山继承下来
these will be my inheritance.
哦 不不 这些我要带走的
Oh, no no. These are qoing with me.
没错 要跟着我进棺材的
Yeah, these are my coffin shoes.
死人也要走路的
Dead man walkinq!
哇哦 我去 这鞋好牛
Ooh, now, these are fire.
你知道这双值多少吗
You know how much these are worth?
我知道 你给我退后
I do. Now, back up.
可远观而不可亵玩 兄弟
Look but don't touch, my brother.
天 你怎么跟奢侈品店的柜姐一个口气
Wow. You sound like the lady at the jewelry store.
-嘿 马蒂  -嘿
Hey, Martv. Hey.
你衣服上是什么
Um, what's on your shirt?
啊 这个啊
Ah, this.
是墨西哥卷饼
It's a burrito
要给你个围兜吗 老弟
Do you need a bib, bro?
不不不 不是我吃的卷饼 是这样的
No. No, it is not my burrito. You see,
某位孕妇正在吃卷饼
a certain preqnant woman was eating it
我只是无辜地问了一句
and I just innocently asked
她这种状况吃这个会不会太辣 下一秒
if it was too spicy for someone in her condition, and she.
她就朝你丢了卷饼
She threw it at you?
不不不
Oh, no. No.
她温柔地把它戳在我胸口 划了下来
She qently mushed it on mv chest and slid it down.
你去告诉一个孕妇该怎么忌口
So, you told a preqnant woman what she can't eat?
得亏她没为难你
You qot off easy.
我是被人泼过一锅热秋葵汤的
I qot a pot of hot qumbo thrown at me.
你以为自己会比秋葵汤跑得快 事实证明不是
You think vou'd be faster than qumbo, but nope.
好吧 也许我能向你取取经
Oh, well, mavbe you can help me out.
你已经当爸了
You're a- a baby daddv.
仨娃了
Of three.
来自三个不同的女人
From three different women.
这不能怪我啊
Hey, don't be mad at me
谁叫我魅力十足呢
cause I'm lovable.
总之 你是如何跟一个没有
Anyway, how do you co- parent
和你在一起的人共同抚养孩子的
with somebodv who you're not with?
我和考特尼是朋友
I mean, Courtney and I are friends, sure,
但我们没在约会 考虑到她对我的态度
but we're not a couple, and the way she treats me now,
我在她心中可能是个捐精人
I might as well be a sperm donor.
听着 马蒂 既然你俩没有男女关系
Look, Marty because you and Courtney aren't
你就应该有话直说
in a relationship, you shouldn't be afraid to put your foot down.
但要注意方式 因为你俩还是有关系的
But qently, because vou are in a relationship.
只是没有男女那一步
You iust aren't havinq sex with her.
说的有点道理
That kind of makes sense.
有吗
Does it?
当然有了
Well, yeah, man.
但你不会明白的 因为你没进俱乐部
Well, you wouldn't understand'cause you're not in our club.
-什么俱乐部  -孩子爹俱乐部
What club? The baby daddv's club.
还有这种说法
That's not a thinq.
有啊 听着
It is. Look, look, look.
马蒂 别在乎马尔科姆怎么说
Marty, don't worry about Malcolm.
有孩子是一种福气 你会处理好的
Kids are a blessing. You're qonna work this out.
谢谢老哥
Thanks, man.
呃 特雷
Uh, Trey?
你穿着我爸的鞋要去哪
Where are you qoinq with our pop's shoes on?
诶 怪了 我进门时穿得不是这双吗
Oh, that's weird. I ain't come in with these?
你好
Ah, hello.
你一定是估价师斯科特吧
You must be Scott the appraiser.
欢迎光临
Welcome to our home.
我们是巴特勒一家
We are the Butlers.
你们家真漂亮 巴特勒先生
You've got a beautiful home, Mr. Butler.
哦 对
Oh, right, uh
巴特勒先生当然在此
Mr. Butler, of course.
你可以叫我卡尔文
Uh, you know what, call me Calvin.
对 蒂娜·巴特勒 就是这位
Yeah, Tina Butler- who- who's riqht here- -
厨房是我们自己设计的
and I desiqned this kitchen ourselves.
我们厨房里只会放格兰诺拉麦片
And you'll notice we onlv have qranola
和苹果酱
and applesauce in there.
没什么
No, uh
玉米粉或辣酱
grits or hot sauce.
哦 你很爱听三大肯尼的歌啊
Oh, I see you qot all the Kenny's.
当然了
Sure- sure do.
看看是谁来了
Ah! Look who it is.
我们的儿子 蒂米·巴特勒
It's our son, Timmy Butler.
您好 阁下
Hello gov'nor.
需要来点茶吗
Care for a spot of tea?
蒂米 你为什么要这样说话
Timmv, why are you talking like that?
因为我是白种人啊 不是吗
Well, I'ma Caucasian, I am.
谢谢了您内
Cheerio.
道格 那个杂志 杂志
Douq, maqazine, magazine.
倒霉催的
Blimey!
嗯 考特尼
Uh, Courtney?
考特尼 我能跟你谈谈吗
Courtnev, can I talk to you for a sec?
马蒂 这不是大麻软糖
Marty, they're reqular qummies.
我可以给你看包装
I can show you the bag.
不
No.
不需要
No, uh, no need.
虽然
Uh, althouqh...
明胶是由猪骨头和玉米糖浆
qelatin is made from piq bones
制成的 不过 你随便吃
and corn syrup, but...but- but knock yourself out.
好吧
Okay.
我想说的是
Uh, okay so here's the thing.
咱俩得弄清楚今后怎么办
You and I need to fiqure out what we are.
考特尼 我不想感觉自己只是个捐精人
Courtnev, I- I don't want to feel like a sperm donor.
尽管我会很抢手的
Althouqh I would be a hot commodity.
我身高6英尺
I am six feet tall.
有硕士学位
I have a master's deqree.
发际线还健在
And I still qot all my hair.
马蒂 我不确定你想说啥
Marty, I don't know where this is qoing,
但你的精子已经免费归我了
but I alreadv qot vour sperm for free.
是啊 顺便说一下 不客气
Yeah. And you're welcome for that, by the wav.
但是 呃
But, uh, but
我们需要弄清楚
we need to fiqure out
在你怀孕这事上 我们该怎么合作
how we re qonna work toqether on this whole pregnancy thinq.
-说得对  -先听我说完你再
You're riqht. Just hear me out before vou
哦 哦 我终于说得对了
I'm- I'm right.
是的
Yeah.
我确实需要帮助
I do need help.
这是我有生以来第一次不知该怎么办
For the first time in my life, I don't have all the answers,
我也很无措
and it is freakinq me out.
可是马蒂 我不能接受
But, Marty, I can't have you tryinq
接下来六个月生活都活在你的干涉之下
to micromanaqe my life for the next six months
甚至是接下来18年
and the next 18 vears.
我知道 我可以很烦人
I know, I know, and I can be a lot.
但我在想
But I was thinking,
你还记得我们在喷气推进实验室多么合作无间吗
do you remember how well we worked toqether at JPL?
当然
Yeah.
在火星着陆器项目里我们大放异彩
We killed it on that Mars lander project.
没错 我们成功了
No, we did! We did.
如果我们有办法用机械爪
And if we can qet a robotic claw
在另一个星球上捡石头
to pick up a rock on another planet,
我们当然有办法养个宝宝
we can fiqure out how to have a baby.
说的太对了
Hell yeah! Yeah.
我们一定能成功
We can do this.
我们可以叫它
Yeah. We can call it
宝宝行动
Operation Baby.
你这么郑重的停顿 我还以为你能起个更好的名字
You know, with the pause, I was expectinq a better name,
但随你咯
but sure.
你听那些肯尼的音乐了吗
So, did you listen to the Kenny's?
我对那个肯尼·G反正挺无感
Yeah, well, I'm not mad at that Kennv G.
第二次估价出来了
The second appraisal's in.
妈妈有定制卫生间咯
Mama's qonna qet her wet room.
谢谢你 白皮巴特勒
Oh, thank you, white Butlers.
能演你和卡尔文很荣幸
Well, it was an honor to be you and Calvin.
来吧 我们开始选瓷砖吧
Come on, let's start picking out some tiles.
其实吧
Yeah...
其实吧是什么意思
Yeah...what?
我们不能拿那笔钱
We can't take that money.
为什么 是你赢了啊
What's wrong? You won.
不 我们没赢
No, we didn't.
是你为我们赢了
You won for us.
如果我们接受这笔钱
And if we accept that money,
传达了我们的什么态度
then what would we be saying-
他们的种族歧视政策是对的
that their racist policies are okay?
不 不
No, no.
不对 但是你知道
Not okay, but you know
怎样才能消除你心里的疙瘩吗
what would take the sting out of it?
一个坐浴盆
A bidet
感受那股暖流吹在你的屁股上
that blows warm air on your tush.
天啊 我是说
Oh, my God, I mean...
得了吧 蒂娜 不行
Come on, Tina, no.
听着 妈 如果你拿了他们的钱
Look, Ma Ma if vou take their money,
相当于你被他们收买了
you're iust letting them buy you off.
听着 爸 我们得做点什么 让他们别妄想
Look, Pop, we qot to do somethinq so they don't think
可以逃过一劫
they can iust qet away with this.
你说得对 儿子
You're riqht, son.
我同意
I aqree.
等新瓷砖铺完了
And we'll do that the second
我们再动手不行吗
they finish grouting the new tile.
好吧 挪我负责从午夜到凌晨五点
Okav, soYwill take bottle feeding
用奶瓶喂孩子
from midniqht to 5. 00 a. m
很好 我负责喂母乳
Great, and I'll do nursinq.
那当然
Obviouslv.
吐奶我负责  流口水你负责
Iwill do spit up, you do drool.
拉臭臭我们一起上
We both do poop.
hlai清理臭臭 人人有责
人人都难逃臭臭
Everybody qets poop.
我觉得咱们搞定了
Uh, yo Ithink we nailed this.
是啊 我们肯定是很棒的父母
Yeah, we're qonna be awesome co- parents.
我饿死了 午餐吃什么
I am starving. What's for lunch? Ooh!
拉面 墨西哥菜
Ramen. Mexican.
再开一局吧
New board.
下午好
Good afternoon,
先生太太们
Mr. And Mrs.
是巴特勒吗
Butler?
不好意思 到底谁是巴特勒家
I'm sorrv, who are the Butlers?
抱歉 对不起 我都糊涂了
Excuse me, sorry. I'm- I'm confused.
你们的名字是都一样吗
Do you all have the same name?
其实 我们才是真正的巴特勒一家
Actuallv, look, we are the real Butlers.
你的银行派人来看了我们的房子
And your bank came to our house
却给了一个相当低的估价
to give us an appraisal, and it was quite low.
所以 为了第二次估价
So, for the second appraisal,
我们让我们的朋友假扮巴特勒一家
we had our friends be the Butlers
但他们的估价变高了
and their appraisal was higher
明明是同一栋该死的房子
for the same damn house.
所以
So
你看出这两个版本的
do you see a difference
巴特勒一家的区别了吗
between these two sets of Butlers?
你是说 身高吗
you mean, like, height- wise?
是哦
Yeah.
谁的身高更黑呢
Whose height is darker?
我敢肯定这只是
I'm sure that this was just some kind
某种误会 我向你保证
of a misunderstanding, and I promise you,
我们一定会调查为何会发生这种事
we're qonna look into how this happened.
不 她刚刚
Oh, no, she did not
-把那个文件夹合上了  -没错 她合上了
iust close that folder. Yes, she did.
你知道吗 女上 不用你去
You know what, ma'am, you don't- you don't have to
调查为什么有这种事
look into how this happened.
我们都知道为什么有这种事
We know how this happened.
我们巴特勒一家全员
All of us Butlers
都知道为什么有这种事
know how this happened.
好了 戴夫 你可以不用演了
Okay, Dave, we're dropping that part.
很显然 失误已经发生了
Clearlv, mistakes were made.
但我向你们保证 我们会纠正这个问题的
But I assure you that we're gonna make this right.
世界上还真有人相信
Whv in the world would they trust
这家银行的花言巧语吗
anything this bank says now?
没错 我们必须赢得你们的信任
You're riqht. We have to earn that trust.
所以 首先 理所当然
So, first thing, obviously,
我们会承认更高的估价
we will honor the higher appraisal.
想得美 这不是钱的问题
You know what? Nice trv, but this isn't about money.
这是是非的问题
This is about the right and the wronq.
大是大非就是SGV银信的全部坚守
Right and wrong is what SGV Bank &Trust is all about.
所以 请别因为一颗老鼠屎
So, please don't judqe our actions
就坏了我们整锅粥
bv one bad apple.
看来你这口破锅里的
Well, there seems to be a lot of bad apples
老鼠屎着实不少
from a verv old and rotten tree.
-珍玛  -开录
Gemma. On it
-嗨  -你好啊
Hi. Hello. Hi.
这些人是谁
Who are these people?
这些人吗
Oh, these people?
真是个好问题
That's a qood question.
我做了一些调查
You know, I did a little digging around
我发现我们这个社区有很多人
and Ifound out that a whole bunch of people
在你这家银行有抵押贷款
in our neighborhood have mortgaqes with this bank.
您猜怎么着
And quess what?
他们的估价都低于平均水平
They all qot appraisals way below the averaqe.
现在 你注意到这些人有什么共同点吗
Now, do you notice any unifving characteristics here?
我们身高都差不多吗
Yeah. Are we all the same heiqht?
我向你保证
I assure you,
如果发生了这样的事 我很抱歉
if that happened, I am very sorry.
本银行致力于维护种族平等
This bank is committed to equality.
我听到的不是这样
That's not what heard.
好吧 好吧
Yeah. Okay, okay.
你是否愿意
Well, are you willing to promise
在上帝和珍玛的手机面前保证
in front of God and Gemma's phone Mm.
你会为这些人的房子
that you will order new appraisals
-重新安排估价  -妥妥的
for all these people's houses? Of course.
-他们能做到公平吗  -绝对的
And that they will be fair? Absolutely.
你会免了我们的停车费吗
And that you will validate our parking?
因为你让我们等了 大概 20分钟
Because you made us wait, like, 20 minutes
这加起来可不少呢
and. and it adds up.
很抱歉 这栋楼不是我们的
I'm sorrv, we don't own the building.
真是个
Isn't that
方便的借口
convenient?
你知道吗
You know what?
在我们决定公开这件事之前
You qot three days to make this right
你有三天的时间来纠正错误
before we decide to make this thing public.
我儿子社交账户上的粉丝
And my son has a disturbing number
多的让人心惊肉跳喔
of social media followers.
明白了 好吧
Understood. Okay.
请大家都跟我
if you quys will all...Well, you just follow me
到人厅去 我去找些资料
to the lobby and I will qet some information
然后我们会持续推进这件事的 好吗
and then we will...we will qet thinqs rollinq on this, okav?
-我为你骄傲 马尔科姆  -我也为你骄傲 爸爸
I'm proud of you, Malcolm. Im proud of you, too, Pop.
谢谢你 儿子
Oh, thank you, son.
-蒂娜 来吧  -别别
Tina, come on. No. No, no no no, no
至于淋浴花洒 有雨点式
And for the shower, it has rain,
瀑布式 喷雾式 还有按摩式
waterfall, mist, ooh, and massaqe.
能满足我所有的爽点吗
Mm, will it hit all my hot spots?
一个不漏
Mm, every one.
哪怕是你还没开发的爽点
Even the ones you didn't know you had.
好吧 开始下单吧 宝贝
Hey, well, qet to ordering, babe.
那么 你们是从哪家银行拿到贷款的
Hev so uh, which bank did you guvs get the loan from?
不找银行了
No bank.
我们有自己的资源
Why should we qo beqging for money
为什么还要去讨钱呢
when we have our own resources?
好吧 什么资源
All riqht What resources?
马尔科姆 你应该先坐下来
Um, Malcolm, you should sit down.
-我吗  -是的
M- Me? Yeah.
怎么了
What is it?
好吧 真的很难以启齿
Well, there's no easy way to say this,
但是呢 我把乔丹4运运动鞋卖了
but, uh, I sold the Jordan 4s.
别卖4s啊 爸爸
Not the 4s, Pop.
还不止
There's more.
限量版 耐克篮球鞋
The limited edition, uh, Nike Dunks?
卖了
Gone.
-你没事吧  -你去哪 马尔科姆
You okay? Where you qoing, Malcolm?
我是个成年人了 妈妈
I'm a qrown man, Mama.
我不会当你们面哭泣的
I ain't qonna cry in front of v'all.
马尔科姆
Malcolm.
老娘还想买加热毛巾架呢
I was thinking about the heated towel racks.